Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979
Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979.
37-1-1384
Cornell University. Office of the Dean of Students.
16.3 cubic ft.
Reports, correspondence, surveys, meeting minutes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Subject files, annual reports, correspondence, surveys, and other administrative files of the Dean of Students; includes fraternity and sorority matters records.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, annual reports, correspondence, surveys, and other administrative files of the Dean of Students; includes fraternity and sorority matters records.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Office of the Dean of Students.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #37-1-1103 and #37-1-1168.
CONTAINER LIST
  - Subject Files, 1940-1964 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1951-1966 (Box 2)
  - Women's Student Government Association (WSGA) ms volume, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - WSGA Subject Files and related items, 1956-1963 (Box 3)
  - Outgoing Correspondence arranged chronologically, 1964-1966 (Box 4)
  - WSGA Financial Records, 1952-1963 (Box 4)
  - Misc. WSGA records, n.d. (Box 5)
  - WSGA Subject Files, 1951-1964 (Box 6)
  - Misc. office files, 1965-1975 (Box 7)
  - Misc. office files, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Student satisfaction survey 1978, March 1979 (Box 8)
    21 pages, mimeograph. Part I. "Survey of Attitudes and Satisfactions of Class of '78 Graduates"
  - Not described (Box 9-10)